{"data":[{"question":"Our present financial problems will soon been a thing of the past.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"financial","b":"problems","c":"been","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"- Been-> be","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"I spoke to Colonel and Mrs. Tibbs only since last week, just before they died in that terrible train accident.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to","b":"since","c":"just","d":"terrible","answer":"2","explain":"- Since-> in","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"When I bought it, I thought it was a beautiful color, but I don't like it any much.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"thought","c":"a","d":"much","answer":"4","explain":"- Much->more","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"If we wait long, we will get what we do want.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wait","b":"will get","c":"what","d":"do","answer":"4","explain":"- Do-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"We have been thought the matter over and have finally come to a decision.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"thought","b":"over","c":"finally","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"- Been thought-> thought","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"The first thing we notice about this people is that their needs were not at all supernatural.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"thing","b":"this","c":"is","d":"at all","answer":"2","explain":"- This-> these","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"Cheques should only be accept with proof of identity.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"only","b":"accept","c":"of","d":"identity","answer":"2","explain":"- Accept-> accepted","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"People no longer smoke so much cigarettes as they used to.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"no longer","b":"so much","c":"as","d":"used to","answer":"2","explain":"- So much-> so many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"It's not necessary to have any previous experience to apply in the job.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to have","b":"any","c":"experience","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":"- In-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"},{"question":"It would not be surprising if some form of memory of such an important events should survive to this day.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would","b":"memory","c":"events","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"- Events-> event","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"10","type":"1"}]}